rugstudio.com 2010-12-05

# RugStudio: Privacy Policy

|  |  | | |   
---|---|---  
| 

|   
---  
| 

Effective: 12/12/99  
  
---  

Our Commitment To Privacy   
The Information We Collect   
How We Use Information   
Our Use of Cookie Information   
Our Commitment To Data Security   
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy   
How To Access Or Correct Your Information   
How To Contact Us  

** ** Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Additionally, the successful submission of an online order depends upon your submission of individually identifiable information.  

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the RugStudio.com website (www.RugStudio.com). On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive information and materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Full name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information  
Comments

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** With your permission, we occasionally send you information about new products and services, or offers that we feel may be of interest to you.

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order.

We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can[register](http://www.rugstudio.com/index.asp?PageAction=LOGIN)with our website, or[login](http://www.rugstudio.com/index.asp?PageAction=LOGIN)to your existing account, if you would like to receive additional information or updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser the number of individuals visiting a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** Cookies are small packets of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not collect personally identifying information, nor are they associated with any information that could be used to identify you. We use cookies to provide features such as Search. Although these cookies are necessary to complete transactions at RugStudio.com, they are immediately sent back to the server and do not remain on your hard drive.

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. When you place orders or access your account information, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. All customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us directly, as described below. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

BACK TO TOP  
  
** ** Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies... [ click here to contact us ](http://www.rugstudio.com/index.asp?PageAction=CONTACTUS) .

BACK TO TOP  
  
| |
